(Sheldon:)As if one of the plants
from
Invasion of the Body Snatchers
(Sheldon:)duplicated you in every way,
(Sheldon:)only with an absurd
amount of hair gel.
(Sheldon:)What are you
working on?
(Sheldon:)I'm removing
my digital footprint
(Sheldon:)from the Internet
(Sheldon:)so Amy Farrah Fowler
can't find me
(Sheldon:)and compel me to meet her mother.
Ah.
(Leonard:)You're going off the grid.
(Sheldon:)Exactly.
(Leonard:)The old Unabomber approach.
Kudos.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)I've also sent Amy a
relationship termination notice
(Sheldon:)and changed my cell phone number
and e-mail address.
(Leonard:)What if she just comes over?
(Sheldon:)She'll get lost.
(Sheldon:)We no longer live
at 2311 Los Robles.
(Sheldon:)We now live at 311 Los Robles.
(Leonard:)You changed the address
on the building?
(Leonard:)What about mail?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no worries--
I explained my predicament
(Sheldon:)to our letter carrier.
(Sheldon:)He was sympathetic.
His exact words were:
"Got your back, Jack.
Bitches be crazy."